[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
♪ I don't really like it
When people keep flirting with me ♪
♪ You approach me first
But why do you disappear in the end? ♪
♪ You act playful but never serious ♪
♪ You'll see if you're not careful ♪
♪ If you get ruined, it'll be too late to blame me ♪
♪ I'm warning you, don't think you're so good ♪
♪ Don't think everyone will lose to you ♪
♪ I've met a lot of people like you ♪
♪ I can see through you ♪
♪ Come on, baby, I'll show you ♪
♪ Eyes on me ♪
♪ Keep your eyes on me ♪
♪ Learn what the real deals do
When they play with people's hearts ♪
♪ Eyes on me ♪
♪ Keep your eyes on me ♪
♪ I'll show you ♪
(The previous week)
Alright, and this is the perspective
from the Entrepreneur of the Year award winner,
Ms. Phakinee Traisuvetthiwat,
the talented daughter of Mr. Phakpoom,
one of Asia's wealthiest men.
He's absolutely confident...
This one?
that she will be able to lead the family business
into the global market.
Excuse me.
That's mine.
Miss.
Can I have my scarf back?
Thank you.
Oh?
It's you.
You came here alone?
Yes.
You don't accept things from strangers, right?
But we've met twice.
I guess we're no longer strangers.
But you're a woman. You should be careful.
You can't tell people's intentions these days.
Are you one of those people?
If you have to be careful,
why are you sitting here alone in the dark?
Why don't you go sit in a nice bar
with good music?
It should be much more fun than sitting here.
I don't like it.
I prefer to sit in a place like this.
I'm much happier here.
It's strange.
There's another person
who likes to come to Pattaya
just to sit and listen to the waves like me.
I like to sit idly by the sea like an idiot too.
Sit idly like an idiot?
Are you coming to sit idly like an idiot
around here again tomorrow?
If I feel bored, I might come.
Let me think about it.
Well, then...
Can I walk you back?
It's far, right?
I didn't say that.
- The clients.
- Hey, girls.
Hey, girls.
What's wrong?
- Girls.
- I got the direction wrong.
We should go that way.
Uh, girls.
It's late. Want us to accompany you?
Save your energy,
so you can take your fathers to the hospital.
With that kind of attitude, I think we need to
take you up to a room to teach you some manners.
I think your mouths will be used
for holding coins instead of talking soon.
You did that twice, bitch.
Where did they go? They ran so fast.
They're small but so freaking fast.
They ran so fast.
Oh.
Oh?
It's torn.
And how are you going back?
It's fine. I can walk.
Hey, wait.
Let me help you.
You'll hurt your feet if you walk yourself.
Like every wave will
Find it’s way back into the big blue
I will find my way to you
And like a harvest moon
Turn from darkness into gold
That’s when you’ll know
That you’ll find home
So here we go
Now slowly open up your eyes
Let me be your guide
Stepping stones together
Do you see now
You’re still that child
Just leave me here.
But this is where we were earlier?
Yeah, thank you for bringing me here.
Uh, wait.
If you're not doing anything tomorrow,
let's go do something fun.
Did I keep you waiting long?
No, not long.
You've been working really hard, haven't you?
You can tell?
It's very easy to tell when someone is tired.
Why don't you take off your shoes?
The sand is warm, right?
If you keep running
and never stop to look along the way,
you'll never realize how wonderful it is
to see and experience
the beautiful nature around you.
You seem to understand life very well.
I understand it.
But I can't choose.
I've been running since I was a kid.
Even when I'm tired, I have to pretend I'm not.
I've forgotten what it's like to take a break.
But these two days, you've made me feel like
I'm really getting a break.
I get to smile. I get to laugh.
I get to be myself.
I don't know when I'll get to feel this way again.
You don't know when?
That's right.
I don't know what's waiting for me
when I get back.
At least you can relax today.
Just make the most of it.
♪ Because I feel safe when you're around ♪
♪ Without you, where would I be? ♪
♪ You're my safe zone ♪
♪ I hate to be alone ♪
♪ Can we go back to how we were? ♪
- Excuse me?
- Because I feel...
- Yes?
- Can I request a song called "Glad to?"
Sure.
♪ You don't need to think of me ♪
♪ When you're happy ♪
♪ Just tell me when you feel lonely ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ You don't need me ♪
♪ If you feel comfortable there ♪
♪ If you get hurt,
I'll be there to wipe away your tears ♪
♪ Even when the sky is starless,
You'll still have me ♪
♪ Even on days when you see no one,
You'll still find me ♪
♪ Even on days when the world seems cruel to you,
I'll still be holding your hand ♪
♪ You don't need to give me anything ♪
♪ Because I don't want anything ♪
♪ Just let me stay by your side forever ♪
♪ Just your smile is enough to make my heart happy ♪
♪ I'll stay right here, never far away ♪
♪ If one day you want to love me, I'll be happy too ♪
It's the first time
someone did something like that for me.
I'm so happy
that I got to be your first.
It's my first time too,
doing something like this.
And why did you do it?
I guess I wanted to make you happy.
I want you to have the strength
to fight whatever makes you tired.
I don't want you to feel discouraged.
Maybe,
those up there sent us down to meet each other,
so we can heal each other.
I think those up there just want us to get wet.
My hotel is nearby.
Shall we wait for the rain to stop in my room?
We still don't know each other's names.
I'm Parn.
I'm Peem.
You don't drink?
I don't drink much.
I just want to have a drink with you.
I'll leave once the rain stops.
Don't.
You look so beautiful today, you know that?
♪ Then you ♪
♪ Feel it rushing and lose control ♪
♪ You don't wanna go slow ♪
♪ For sure ♪
♪ We both already know ♪
♪ Your place is my place now ♪
♪ My place is your place ♪
♪ Let's face it ♪
♪ Baby, you know all the places ♪
You're not okay with this?
I just have never done it before.
Then let's start with something light today.
♪ We both said some awful words ♪
♪ And I know that we both got hurt ♪
♪ But I wanna be with you ♪
♪ I wanna be with you ♪
♪ We can't let this slip away ♪
♪ You know that I want you to stay ♪
♪ 'Cause I wanna be with you ♪
♪ I wanna be with you ♪
♪ Don't run away ♪
♪ We can't let this go to waste ♪
♪ I don't want nobody else ♪
♪ Don't let this go to waste ♪
♪ Baby, we can work it out ♪
♪ Maybe you can stay the night ♪
♪ I wanna be with you
I wanna be with you ♪
♪ Don't let this go to waste ♪
♪ I don't wanna let you go
I just wanna let you know ♪
♪ I wanna be with you ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ I hope that we can work it out ♪
♪ But I know that you have your doubts ♪
♪ I wanna be with you ♪
♪ Don't you wanna be with me? ♪
♪ I think about you night and day ♪
♪ And I just want you here with me ♪
♪ I wanna be with you ♪
♪ You know it is the truth ♪
♪ Don't run away
We can't let this go to waste ♪
♪ I don't want nobody else, else ♪
♪ Don't let this go to waste ♪
You don't need to do anything.
I'll do it for you.
♪ Don't let this go to waste ♪
♪ I don't wanna let you go ♪
♪ I just wanna let you know ♪
♪ I wanna be with you ♪
♪ Don't let this go to waste ♪
♪ Baby, we can work it out ♪
♪ Wanna feel you close to me ♪
♪ Don't let this go to waste ♪
♪ I know that we can work it out ♪
♪ To waste ♪
♪ Wanna feel you close to me ♪
Yes, Mom.
Parn?
Peem.
Hm?
What are you thinking about?
You've been zoning out a lot
since you got back from the beach.
Zoning out?
If you hadn't been zoning out,
would you be standing here?
The meeting.
Right, there's a meeting.
Mmm.
This project will be
a new destination in the city.
The concept is to make green spaces
the heart of this project.
The hotel won't just be a place to stay,
but a part of the experience
from the moment you step in.
And if we succeed,
this project will be a landmark that will
completely change the image of life in this city.
Good job, sweetie.
I was right to trust you to handle this project.
But don't forget that
we can't run the hotel ourselves.
You have to find a way to get Mr. Songsak,
the owner of the six-star hotel chain,
to invest with us.
Yes.
Mm.
Hey.
It's not going to be easy with Mr. Songsak.
He has high standards.
He's so freaking picky and meticulous.
If he feels our project isn't exceptional,
he won't take the risk.
If our project needs him, I will get him.
This job is difficult,
but it'd be easier if you had help from Angel
from Paradise Club Bangkok.
I heard Mr. Songsak is infatuated with her.
If you can get her to join the table,
I'm sure the project will succeed.
If you don't believe me, go see for yourself.
I've reserved a table for you tonight.
A woman who can be bought with money
won't be difficult to deal with.
Hey, Parn.
Mr. Tot is here to see you again.
Mr. Tot is a widower. His wife is dead. He's rich.
You can have a good life and a good family.
If you want to leave this place,
I think he's a good way out.
I told you many times.
No.
Okay, well, there's a VVIP guest tonight.
Same table.
Do whatever it takes to get him to spend
as much money as possible.
Do you understand, my Angel?
Even if I get married
and try to clear my image,
everyone will still think I'm a high-class whore.
Hurry up, the guests are coming.
Please give it up for Angel of Paradise!
Let's start the bidding.
Let's begin now!
Fifty drinks.
One hundred drinks.
Two hundred drinks.
Three hundred drinks.
Five hundred.
Is it 500 baht or 500 drinks, sir?
Five hundred drinks.
Tonight, Angel must be with me.
Five hundred going once.
Five hundred going twice.
Anyone wants to give more than Mr. Tot?
Five hundred...
Thrice. Angel will be with Mr. Tot tonight!
Why is he so freaking rich?
How the hell would I know?
But don't waste your money.
You can only get one hour with 35,000 baht.
She's as beautiful as an angel.
Even if you spend hundreds of thousands,
you still won't get to touch her arm.
Yeah.
For someone like that,
you gotta pay millions to get her.
Of course. A woman like this
have to be bought with money, right?
Yeah.
Cheers, man.
Let's drink, man.
Let me take a sip.
We have our stuff tonight, here.
Just leave, both of you.
I don't want to drink.
But I...
You don't remember my rules?
You're a friend to talk to, not to sleep with.
But I spent a lot on you, Parn.
When will you let me?
If you let me, I'll buy you a house, a car.
I'll give you everything.
And I'll quit the nightlife
for the rest of my life.
Come on, Sis.
Over there.
Oh.
Ms.
What are you looking for?
I want to see Angel. How much do I have to pay?
Ouch.
What's wrong?
Something got in my eye.
Come on, let me see.
Two thousand drinks.
Is that enough to keep you with me all night?
Did you misunderstand something?
The bidding was already over.
Tonight,
Parn must be with me.
Wait, Ms., where are you going?
I'm buying 2,000 drinks. Let Angel be with me.
You can't do that. I won the bidding.
And I paid the whole amount.
Don't you want 2,000 drinks?
Or are you too stupid to tell,
between 500 drinks and 2,000 drinks,
which one is more?
You don't answer because it's not enough, right?
Then I'll buy 5,000 drinks, and you
stay with me all night. Do we have a deal?
Million... That's over a million.
Isn't that over a million?
Can you transfer the money now?
Hey.
Are you really going with her?
Well, I want her money.
Sis, can you transfer the money now?
You're rushing it
because of your dad again, right?
I paid off everything last time they beat Mom up.
Why did you get a loan from them?
Why didn't you tell me?
Why get a loan from loan sharks?
Quit nagging me.
And don't expect me to be grateful to you.
You're the one who should be grateful to me.
I'm not demanding your gratitude.
I'm just saying that
if you need anything, tell me.
Don't get a loan from loan sharks.
It's because I don't want your dirty money.
You don't want it,
but you keep calling me to ask for it.
Your dad got sick.
Your sibling didn't have enough money.
They wanted to borrow 200,000
to put a down payment on a car.
You keep asking me for everything!
Parn! You're insulting me?!
Calm down.
Honey, she's tired. She just wanted to vent.
I wasn't venting. I was telling the truth.
If my money is dirty,
don't call me and ask me to pay your debt.
What a smartmouth!
Honey, don't!
Honey. Honey, don't.
Please don't hurt her.
You ungrateful child.
Don't you remember?
My family is poor as hell now because of you.
Your mother spent every baht
on your medical treatment.
Otherwise, a sickly kid like you
wouldn't be alive now to insult me ​​like this.
What?
You can't stand hearing that, huh?
You can make money now.
I just asked for a little bit of money
and you're insulting me?
Please calm down.
Hey.
Where's the money?
You said you're going to pay me today.
I'm trying to find it.
You've been saying that for three days.
Where's the money?
Please give me a little more time.
I'll find it for you.
Damn it.
Don't!
So what now?
You wanna save your wife?
If you don't pay your debt today,
I'll shoot your mother.
Can you give me a little more time?
Tomorrow, I'll give you the money.
If the money isn't ready tomorrow,
you can prepare for a funeral.
Mom.
It's okay, Mom.
Tomorrow, I'll find you the money.
You parents think you're a walking ATM?
Just transfer me the money.
I need to hurry and pay them.
I'm running out of time.
Alright.
Thank you.
Why isn't she coming out?
What took you so long? Why?
You weren't satisfied back there?
It's not that.
Five hundred drinks and you're making out.
I paid for 5,000 drinks.
I guess I can do more than that.
Get in the car.
Where are you taking me?
I'm not going to murder you.
You'll see when you get there.
If a meal costs 35,000, how much
do I have to pay to sleep with you?
How much do you normally charge?
If I want you, how much do I have to pay?
What's gotten into you?
You're not like the person I met the other day.
You're also not like the person
I met the other day.
At the beach, you acted all innocent.
There's nothing innocent about an escort.
You can do it if you get paid enough.
It's your job.
Still, you told me you'd never done it.
What a professional you are.
You misunderstood me.
- I never--
- Misunderstood what?
I paid you over a million,
and now you're waiting for me to fuck you.
Are you playing hard to get to raise the price?
How much do you want?
Tell me how much you want. Tell me!
I think I should leave.
Where are you going?
- Let go!
- No!
Tell me how much you want! Tell me!
Ms. Peem!
Name your price and get undressed.
Or do you need my help, huh?
- You need my help?
- Ms. Peem. Ms. Peem.
Listen carefully.
I never sold myself to anyone.
Keep your money and buy someone else,
because your money can't buy me.
Hey, how was last night?
What did she say? Tell me.
I haven't talked to her yet.
What? Didn't you say it's done?
Can we get someone else?
No.
Why?
It's gotta be her.
Let's get someone else.
This one is playing hard to get
to raise the price.
An insider told me that, for this guy,
it has to be Angel from Paradise Club,
and no one else.
And I know Techin wants Mr. Songsak too.
Careful or he'll snatch Angel before you do.
Someone like you can't get her?
She's just an escort.
You can come here often.
There's a show tonight too.
I have a show every week.
Every week?
Every week. I personally selected the best girls.
Come and see.
Where's Parn?
Oh? Ms. Peem.
Hello.
I want to see Parn.
Uh, I'm sorry.
Tonight, Parn is fully booked.
Whatever they paid you, I can pay more.
She really can't come tonight, Ms. Peem.
What can't money buy here?
Well, she really can't come tonight.
I'm very sorry.
I'll wait.
The whole night?
I'm free.
Well, thank you for always helping me.
- Happy birthday to you.
Here's your cake.
Thank you.
What's the point of raising
a child of a whore so well?
Peem.
Hello.
Your dad isn't here with you?
He's coming.
You've grown up beautiful, just like your mother.
The mother who sold her child to Phak?
Who knows if she's even his child?
Peem.
Dad.
Hello, Phak.
I can't stay for the meal.
I have an urgent meeting.
Come on, I'm taking you to another restaurant.
He's probably afraid she'll find out
her mother is a money-hungry whore.
I guess all the whores are hungry for money.
If you're okay with me,
I'll pay you very well.
Come work for me.
I told you I'm not going to.
You're going to be a whore until you die?
Stay with me here tonight.
Are you seeing anyone?
Lover? Partner? Husband?
What are you doing here?
She's here to help
clear all of our family's debts.
You have no right to use my things
to make a living.
Your body belongs to me.
You're not allowed to fuck anyone else
without my permission.
♪ Even though my heart says I love you ♪
♪ Why am I like this? ♪
♪ I don't understand ♪
♪ What's wrong with my mouth and my heart? ♪